channel>
<title>Business News: Latest News on Business, Stock Markets, Financial News, India Business & World Business News</title>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business</link>
<description>Check latest updates on business, finance and economy from across the world. Get daily updates for BSE Sensex, Share price, Stock markets, BSE, NSE, Nifty, business news on various sectors and much more from Times of India Business.</description>
<language>en-gb</language>
<lastBuildDate>2023-11-04T14:07:13+05:30</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link type="application/rss+xml" rel="self" href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/rssfeeds/1898055.cms"/>
<copyright>Copyright:(C) Sat, 04 Nov 2023 14:07:13 IST Bennett Coleman & Co. Ltd, http://in.indiatimes.com/policyterms/1554651.cms</copyright>
<docs>http://syndication.indiatimes.com/</docs>
<image>
<title>Business News: Latest News on Business, Stock Markets, Financial News, India Business & World Business News</title>
<url>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/507610.cms</url>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>'There'll be a point where no job is needed... AI will do all'</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955318.cms" />In a much-hyped conversation between British Prime Minister Rishi Sunak and Tesla CEO Elon Musk at the conclusion of the AI Safety Summit hosted by the UK government, the duo discussed a range of issues from job threats posed by artificial intelligence to how AI-enabled robots could make good "friends" in the future. "We are seeing the most destructive force in history here. There will come a point where no job is needed - you can have a job if you want one for personal satisfaction, but AI will do everything," said Musk.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/therell-be-a-point-where-no-job-is-needed-ai-will-do-all/articleshow/104955318.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/therell-be-a-point-where-no-job-is-needed-ai-will-do-all/articleshow/104955318.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:43:04+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955330,imgsize-23262.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Reliance Retail to acquire Arvind Fashions arm</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955305.cms" />Reliance Retail will acquire Arvind Beauty Brands Retail, a subsidiary of Arvind Fashions that runs the Sephora India business, in a Rs 99 crore all cash deal. As part of the transaction, Reliance's retail arm will take over the operations of Sephora's 26 stores across 13 Indian cities, besides gaining exclusive rights to build Sephora's presence in India across channels, Reliance and Arvind Fashions said in separate filings on Friday. Prestige beauty retail brand Sephora is part of the France head-quartered LVMH Group and operates more than 2700 stores globally.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/reliance-retail-to-acquire-arvind-fashions-arm/articleshow/104955305.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/reliance-retail-to-acquire-arvind-fashions-arm/articleshow/104955305.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:39:32+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955309,imgsize-30878.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sterlite Power set to demerge transmission business</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955281.cms" />Sterlite Power Transmission (SPTL) is demerging its transmission infrastructure business with a view to unlocking value by creating distinct verticals based on consumer base, investor class and return profiles. Under the demerger scheme, existing Sterlite Power shareholders will receive one additional share of SGL5 for every share of SPTL they hold, the company said on Friday. The power transmission infrastructure business has transmission assets in India and Brazil, which will now be transferred to Sterlite Grid 5 Ltd (SGL5). Both SPTL and SGL5 will have independent boards and management teams.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/sterlite-power-set-to-demerge-transmission-business/articleshow/104955281.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/sterlite-power-set-to-demerge-transmission-business/articleshow/104955281.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:35:51+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955298,imgsize-65688.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Services sector activity hits 7-month low in October</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955264.cms" />India's services sector growth slowed down in October to a seven-month low due to weaker output and new business, according to a survey. The seasonally adjusted S&P Global India Services PMI Business Activity Index dropped to 58.4 in October, from 61 in September. The survey revealed subdued demand and competitive conditions as factors impacting growth. However, the data also showed a strong increase in international orders for Indian services companies, particularly from Asia, Europe, and the US. Higher expenses, including food, fuel, and staff costs, also contributed to the slowdown.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/services-sector-activity-hits-7-month-low-in-october/articleshow/104955264.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/services-sector-activity-hits-7-month-low-in-october/articleshow/104955264.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:31:17+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955274,imgsize-67056.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Raymond buys 59% in auto parts co Maini</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955241.cms" />Raymond group has acquired a 59.2% stake in Maini Precision Products for Rs 682 crore through a combination of debt and internal accruals. The transaction will be subject to regulatory approvals and is expected to be completed during the current fiscal. This acquisition is a strategic move to strengthen Raymond's existing engineering business. The consolidated business will cater to the top global original equipment manufacturers and tier-1 manufacturers across aerospace, defence, auto and industrial businesses.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/raymond-buys-59-in-auto-parts-co-maini/articleshow/104955241.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/raymond-buys-59-in-auto-parts-co-maini/articleshow/104955241.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:27:16+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955258,imgsize-36898.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Goldman Sachs promotes 35 in India as MDs</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955223.cms" />Goldman Sachs has promoted 35 employees in India to the managing director (MD) position this year, who will take charge from January 1, next year. There were 4 promotions in its Mumbai office, 26 and 5 promotions respectively in its Bengaluru and Hyderabad offices. About 17% of its employees who're promoted are women, 60% are from finance functions, and 14% are from engineering. In 2021, the firm promoted 29 MDs in India. Globally, Goldman Sachs said 608 individuals across 44 offices have been promoted as managing directors.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/goldman-sachs-promotes-35-in-india-as-mds/articleshow/104955223.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/goldman-sachs-promotes-35-in-india-as-mds/articleshow/104955223.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:23:38+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955232,imgsize-33052.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>UCO Bank calls back 'sweets for NPAs' circular</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955205.cms" />UCO Bank has withdrawn a circular which instructed branch heads to meet with top defaulters and distribute Diwali sweets to them. The circular had sparked significant attention due to its unconventional approach. UCO Bank's MD and CEO, Ashwani Kumar, addressed the matter during a press conference where the bank's quarterly results were announced. "The intention was to break the ice and meet and greet those whose accounts had turned into non-performing assets, but somehow it got captured as distribution of sweets," he said. </description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/uco-bank-calls-back-sweets-for-npas-circular/articleshow/104955205.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/uco-bank-calls-back-sweets-for-npas-circular/articleshow/104955205.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:19:48+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955214,imgsize-25590.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Government's 50-year bond debut sees 4x demand</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104955179.cms" />The Indian government has introduced a 50-year bond worth Rs 10,000 crore for the first time, which saw strong demand. The auction by the RBI received bids worth Rs 40,200 crore from 216 bids. The cut off yield for the bonds was 7.46% per annum. The government had previously announced plans to introduce 50-year gilts in response to demand from insurance companies. Additionally, the government will also introduce sovereign green bonds in its weekly auctions.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/governments-50-year-bond-debut-sees-4x-demand/articleshow/104955179.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/governments-50-year-bond-debut-sees-4x-demand/articleshow/104955179.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T06:15:48+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104955194,imgsize-32292.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Zomato posts 36crore Q2 profit</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104952688.cms" /> Zomato reported net profit of Rs 36 crore on a consolidated basis in the September quarter, marking its second consecutive quarter of profitability. The food delivery firm had posted net profit of Rs 2 crore in the June quarter, largely aided by a tax gain and loss of Rs 251 crore in Q2FY23. "The growth momentum we witnessed in Q1FY24 continued in Q2FY24, driven by healthy growth across all our businesses," founder and CEO Deepinder Goyal said in a letter to shareholders on Friday. </description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/zomato-posts-36crore-q2-profit/articleshow/104952688.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/zomato-posts-36crore-q2-profit/articleshow/104952688.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T02:47:57+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104952691,imgsize-32130.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Infosys says US arm hit by cybersecurity event</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104952663.cms" />Infosys McCamish Systems, a subsidiary of Infosys BPM, reported a "cybersecurity event" that resulted in the non-availability of certain applications and systems. The company is working with a cybersecurity products provider to resolve the issue and has launched an independent investigation. Infosys McCamish provides services to the financial services sector and is a software reseller for industry-specific clients. Meanwhile, Infosys has opened a new centre in Sofia, Bulgaria, to attract and upskill 500 new employees as part of its growth roadmap in Europe.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/infosys-says-us-arm-hit-by-cybersecurity-event/articleshow/104952663.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/infosys-says-us-arm-hit-by-cybersecurity-event/articleshow/104952663.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T02:39:49+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104952686,imgsize-20260.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>AI tech regulation in 5-6 months, says minister of state for IT and Electronics Rajeev Chandrasekhar</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104952639.cms" />India's Minister of State for IT and Electronics, Rajeev Chandrasekhar, has stated that artificial intelligence (AI) should not be demonized and that India will work towards creating an early regulatory framework around it. He emphasized the need for a global consensus on managing challenges related to AI, such as job impact, privacy, weaponization, and criminalization. Chandrasekhar also mentioned the importance of addressing risks and ensuring safety and trust in AI platforms.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/ai-tech-regulation-in-5-6-months-says-minister-of-state-for-it-and-electronics-rajeev-chandrasekhar/articleshow/104952639.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/ai-tech-regulation-in-5-6-months-says-minister-of-state-for-it-and-electronics-rajeev-chandrasekhar/articleshow/104952639.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T02:32:37+05:30</pubDate>
<dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Pankaj Doval</dc:creator>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104952655,imgsize-43572.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>IndiGo logs profit for 4th quarter in row</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104952620.cms" />IndiGo has reported a profit of Rs 189 crore in the September quarter, against a loss of Rs 1,583 crore in Q2 last fiscal. India's largest domestic airline saw its total income rise 21% to Rs 15,503 crore this Q2 from Rs 12,582 crore last year. The airline's capacity increased by 27.7% and passengers carried rose 33.4% to 2.6 crore in the traditionally weakest travel quarter. IndiGo scrip closed flat at Rs 2,509 on the BSE on Friday.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/indigo-logs-profit-for-4th-quarter-in-row/articleshow/104952620.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/indigo-logs-profit-for-4th-quarter-in-row/articleshow/104952620.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T02:26:03+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104952632,imgsize-59824.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple sees record revenue in India amid China woes</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104952599.cms" />Apple CEO Tim Cook praised India's market as an "extraordinary" one, highlighting the company's all-time revenue record in the country. Cook emphasized the potential for growth in India's expanding middle class and expressed satisfaction with the performance of Apple's retail stores in Mumbai and Delhi. Apple's market share in India has been increasing, aided by local manufacturing, competitive pricing, and strong marketing efforts. Cook also mentioned record-breaking achievements in other countries, but declined to compare the growth momentum in India to that of China.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/apple-sees-record-revenue-in-india-amid-china-woes/articleshow/104952599.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/apple-sees-record-revenue-in-india-amid-china-woes/articleshow/104952599.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-04T02:14:28+05:30</pubDate>
<dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Pankaj Doval</dc:creator>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104952604,imgsize-39632.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Why Bain & Co. CEO Manny Maceda thinks India is a compelling investment destination</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104951677.cms" />Manny Maceda, the Worldwide Managing Partner and CEO of Bain & Co. has said, “India has always been a great, unique opportunity.”</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/why-bain-co-ceo-manny-maceda-thinks-india-is-a-compelling-investment-destination/articleshow/104951677.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/why-bain-co-ceo-manny-maceda-thinks-india-is-a-compelling-investment-destination/articleshow/104951677.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T23:48:17+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104951741,imgsize-43430.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>US House easily passes bill to harden sanctions on Iranian oil</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104950990.cms" />The US House of Representatives easily passed a bill on Friday to bolster sanctions on Iranian oil in a strong bipartisan vote. The Stop Harboring Iranian Petroleum (SHIP) bill, which passed 342-69, would impose measures on foreign ports and refineries that process petroleum exported from Iran in violation of US sanctions. US lawmakers are debating several pieces of legislation to pressure Iran after the October 7 attacks on Israel by Hamas that killed at least 1,400 people, mostly civilians. Hamas has long been backed by Iran, but Tehran has denied any involvement in the attacks.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/us-house-easily-passes-bill-to-harden-sanctions-on-iranian-oil/articleshow/104950990.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/us-house-easily-passes-bill-to-harden-sanctions-on-iranian-oil/articleshow/104950990.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T22:39:43+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104951103,imgsize-28636.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Oil heads for weekly loss as geopolitical risk premium wanes</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104950978.cms" />Oil prices fell on Friday as concerns over Middle East tensions eased and US jobs data suggested that the Federal Reserve may not raise interest rates further. Brent crude futures dropped 1.2% to $85.81 a barrel, while US West Texas Intermediate crude futures fell 1.3% to $81.42 a barrel. Both benchmarks were on track for weekly losses of over 5%. In addition, a private sector survey showed that China's services activity expanded at a slightly faster pace in October, but sales grew at the slowest rate in 10 months and employment stagnated.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/oil-heads-for-weekly-loss-as-geopolitical-risk-premium-wanes/articleshow/104950978.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/international-business/oil-heads-for-weekly-loss-as-geopolitical-risk-premium-wanes/articleshow/104950978.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T22:38:35+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104951110,imgsize-289389.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lupin and Zydus partner to combat liver disease and hepatitis</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104950304.cms" />Lupin and Zydus Lifesciences announced they have entered into a licensing and supply agreement to co-market, Saroglitazar Mg for the treatment of non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) and non-alcoholic steato hepatitis (NASH) in India. With a once daily, 4mg dose regimen, Saroglitazar Mg enables better compliance, reduces pill burden, and offers greater convenience for patients, the companies’ said. Lupin will pay Zydus upfront licensing fees and milestone payments based on the achievement of pre-defined milestones.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/lupin-and-zydus-partner-to-combat-liver-disease-and-hepatitis/articleshow/104950304.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/lupin-and-zydus-partner-to-combat-liver-disease-and-hepatitis/articleshow/104950304.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T22:07:01+05:30</pubDate>
<dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Rupali Mukherjee</dc:creator>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104950496,imgsize-10632.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman appreciates SBI for successfully launching direct Lankan-Indian Rupee trade</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104949979.cms" />India's Finance Minister, Nirmala Sitharaman, has praised the State Bank of India (SBI) for launching a direct Sri Lankan Rupee-Indian Rupee trade, making it the first foreign bank in Sri Lanka to do so. Sitharaman inaugurated the second SBI branch in Jaffna during her official visit to Sri Lanka. The initiative aims to provide an alternative to importers of Sri Lanka, reducing dependency on the US Dollar. SBI is also expanding its remittance services in Sri Lanka through its digital platform.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/finance-minister-nirmala-sitharaman-appreciates-sbi-for-successfully-launching-direct-lankan-indian-rupee-trade/articleshow/104949979.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/finance-minister-nirmala-sitharaman-appreciates-sbi-for-successfully-launching-direct-lankan-indian-rupee-trade/articleshow/104949979.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T21:26:34+05:30</pubDate>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104950052,imgsize-43972.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>DGCA asks Pratt to have MRO in India; comp ‘exploring’ feasibility</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104949046.cms" />With Pratt & Whitney engine issues showing no signs of abating, the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has strongly asked the company to have a maintenance, repair and overhaul (MRO) facility in India at the earliest. ​​While new generation PW engines for the Airbus A320neo family of planes — used by IndiGo and erstwhile GoAir — have been having a series of issues for last 5-6 years now, the worst impact is likely to be felt soon with hundreds of these engines going to be grounded for checks globally.</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/troublesome-engines-dgca-asks-pratt-to-have-mro-in-india-company-exploring-feasibility/articleshow/104949046.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/troublesome-engines-dgca-asks-pratt-to-have-mro-in-india-company-exploring-feasibility/articleshow/104949046.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T20:31:23+05:30</pubDate>
<dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Saurabh Sinha</dc:creator>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104949125,imgsize-64472.cms"/>
</item>
<item>
<title>Zomato posts profits for second consecutive quarter; Q2 profit at Rs 36 crore</title>
<description><img border="0" hspace="10" align="left" style="margin-top:3px;margin-right:5px;" src="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/photo/104946083.cms" />Zomato, the food delivery firm, reported net profits of Rs 36 crore in the September quarter, its second consecutive profitable quarter. Revenues increased by 67% year-on-year to Rs 3,060 crore, aiding profitability.​“The growth momentum we witnessed in Q1FY24 continued in Q2FY24 driven by healthy growth across all our businesses,” founder and CEO Deepinder Goyal said in a letter to shareholders on Friday. ​​​ Blinkit’s GOV stood at Rs 2,760 crore in Q2</description>
<link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/zomato-posts-profits-for-second-consecutive-quarter-q2-profit-at-rs-36-crore/articleshow/104946083.cms</link>
<guid>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/business/india-business/zomato-posts-profits-for-second-consecutive-quarter-q2-profit-at-rs-36-crore/articleshow/104946083.cms</guid>
<pubDate>2023-11-03T17:57:32+05:30</pubDate>
<dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Asmita Dey</dc:creator>
<enclosure type="image/jpeg" url="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/msid-104948502,imgsize-21246.cms"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>